man y'all gonna be wasting no time gotta be like i'm in there she live so i saw some folks
that were confused at the post i put up about uh sean king and i wanted to provide some clarity
one thing about me is that um this thing is loud boy okay one thing about me is that
well one my principles are rigid my judgments are flexible and so what i mean by that is that
there's certain things that i have no movement on morning kimmy and there's certain things there's
certain things i have no movement on because they are related to my principles whereas there's other
things that are completely outside of me that would just be about um judgment well they're always
posting me on the shade room because the shade room is a space for division and for the denigration of
black people and so being that i am constantly grounded in the elevation of not only black folks
but of coalition building it behooves them in their goal of denigration to post me when i am uh
you know speaking about things that actually need to be addressed um that fuel their goal of constantly
standing on the side of toxicity so you know that's what they are and the people they said they named me
the shade room for fun yeah like that's what they're about i have asked them repeatedly not to post me
repeatedly um and they have not honored my request so i consider them the ops and um
you know i consider anybody who engages in that space and op and i understand my mission
and that they in no way will stop me from it hollywood unlock they an op too when you have a zionist
supporter hosting events i'm gonna consider you an op when you have an actual person who went on an
ambassador trip to israel hosting an event you're enough period and he probably gonna have something
to say about that and go on a little rant and that would be very oppish of him to do anywho the point
that i was making was around the fact that i am of a mind that anybody who is uh for the resistance
of propaganda used to advance the white nationalist agenda cannot be participating in any way of
legitimizing it and that is a very rigid principle that i stand on i have two podcasts i've had one of
those podcasts for eight years what do you mean why don't i have a podcast i have small doses which
i've had for literally eight years and i have views for amanda land which i do every wednesday
as well on youtube amanda seals tv sometimes the way you all frame things is why you get the response
that you get this is why my bow furrows why don't you have a podcast is like thank you soul delights
so i know some people are like but he was saying it because so and so was saying it in reference to
what did i just say everyone might not know that however it is the framing of the question why don't
you have a podcast is a very um it's a very like what's the word i'm looking for uh aggressive
addressing of a question hey do you have a podcast that i can check out how about that why don't you
have a podcast suggest that i'm doing something that i'm not suggest that i'm not supposed to be
why don't you have a podcast is framed like i'm not doing something that i'm supposed to be doing
accusatory that's the word that's the word that's the word i was looking you saw me looking in the
clouds for it right they're new to me if you're new to me then be quiet and get into it if you're new
to somebody let them be revealed to you y'all want to tell me how to behave like i'm not a 44 year
old woman who's been out here as a public figure since i was eight years old stop trying to give
me unsolicited advice on how to exist i don't need your unsolicited advice to how to exist this is how i
exist this is this is how i exist if you're new to me then take the correction and move along
like i'm not sure y'all want y'all want people that are in your public space to be so graceful with
you but you don't demand that grace of yourselves like i mean you don't demand you don't you don't
demand that grace of yourself to them so you know and y'all like well i took it as it doesn't matter how
you took it they weren't saying it to you it doesn't matter how you took it that's how i took
it i just i i don't understand it well i took it as you mean you who's sitting at home watching other
comments about other people because i promise you the way that you see how other people are being
spoken to versus when when it's being spoken to to you is different perspective is absolutely
going to change how you receive things when a conversation is happening over there
that's not even about you you will one thousand percent receive that different and thank you
the self-centered leo people be slick oh man don't they though
don't they people do be slick baby people do be baby yes the art of sentence structure is dying
is dying are there any hard copies of small doses book available for purchase
yes everywhere they sell books i love how this person thinks that calling me fragile is an insult
you're blocked that's not an insult to me none of you all have any idea what it's like to have
447 people watching and talking to you at the same time who are majority strangers none of you
yeah so i don't expect you to understand anything about what this experience is but i do expect you
to be respectful of the way that i illuminate my experience to you
you're me alexandra smith needs um so as i was saying before you know that is why i um
exactly cancer i am a cancer and that is my superpower so that is why i was saying before
uh that you know when i when principle for me is rigid but judgment is is fluid and i say that
because i would say that principle is grounded in a bottom line um whereas you know judgment about
somebody is tailored specifically to them so for instance um like crystal from the read her judgment
of cardi b you know i found to be really overly harsh and calling her out of her name just seemed
um unnecessary and i think that there may have been you know a genuine concern for wanting the best for
cardi b but it was translated in a way that felt less about um like a loving correction and more
like uh accusational judgment and i feel that for when it comes to me like my judgments about like
personal things are a bit more tailored to the individual's experience versus then my uh principled
responses to when people exist in i don't even want to use the term political but
in like political spaces in terms of like social justice i feel there are just bottom lines
there's not a lot of fluidity there and in terms of uh a liberation stance i feel that there is a bottom
line it's not wavering it's very clear and sharp and that is what makes people feel some type of way
about me a lot of times because they're like oh like she's just too this to that to that and it's not
that it's that i'm not too this that or that i'm very just what it is um whereas judgment to me about
someone's choices in their personal life um it's really like it's their personal life like and i agree
with you sarah asking for nuance about things related to social justice and liberation is a symptom
of fascist society like people will nuance themselves to death you know they'll nuance themselves to death
when you all say things like my heart goes out to the kids as it relates to cardi b i want you to know
how absolutely ridiculous you sound you sound you sound super misogynist super duper misogynist
and you also sound wildly self-righteous this is a person who got to where they are by hard work
like they have success that's consistently been a person engaged in hard work why you would think
that isn't what she's applying to her children is bizarre the the the concept of well she's going on
tour so she can't raise her children i find to be really um an example of misogyny
because it suggests that if she was a dude going on tour you know i don't know if they would have
the same issue however i believe that she has a village around her that is able to supply and
support her when you say she's cosplaying as a black woman i don't necessarily agree with that
she's an afro latina who grew up in the bronx new york and i think for a lot of you all you don't
really understand what the cultural there is a cultural nuance of growing up in new york city
right um so i i just kind of i don't see that that's like i i just i don't i don't see that at all
um i think ultimately she has the resources to not only go on tour with her children but to also
expose them to something outside of the united states which i think is honestly really necessary
to do and i think that um when this person says some person who used to drug and rob men
you know it's funny that people really don't seem to hold people to the same standard all of your
favorite rappers have talked about selling drugs all of them all of your favorite rappers of the 90s
except for maybe like uh native tongues and public enemy have talked about being involved in
lucidious activities and selling drugs all of your favorite presidents have been involved in the acts
of murder of serial killing level murders all of them kamala harris whole genocide and you want to
talk to me about cardi b drugging and robbing men who were paying her for sex i mean i don't think
people have to be um shackled to their pasts i think there's actually something really noble in her
admitting to this uh as her part of her past and to uh standing on it as this was a way that she used
to behave i think that there's something noble in her constant effort to uh move beyond this
and i think that there's a real level of self-righteousness that a lot of people exude
in expecting perfection from people who have gained a certain level of wealth or a certain level of
visibility that they do not apply to themselves i can absolutely say that there are decisions i made
in my 20s as a weaker and in my 30s as a less healed as a less supported as a insecure person
that i am not proud of i however don't believe those decisions shape me as a human on this planet that
i've been on for 44 years so i think that that is i think what's also important is watching
and seeing people atone you know and seeing people um exist differently right there's something that
happens very differently when you're out of certain scenarios of isolation of survival uh you know
there's a really beautiful manifestation of your human ability and and a connection to your soul
that gets to happen right and so we need to be doing more of allowing that to happen earlier i believe
i was i've talked about this in the past like i was on this internet doing the same thing just judging
people and you know you get wrapped up in this whole thing about content and you know this pop culture
commentary when you're really not critiquing commentary you're critiquing character um
crystal's critique about how decisions affect children is incomplete unless she is able to provide
really concrete evidence that the critique is accurate and i think that a woman raising four children
in the same home three of which are with a partner who actually stepped out on her
um and then having a child with someone else that may have happened accidentally uh but choosing to
have that child i think labeling that as somehow an indicator of mistreatment of children is really
um i think it's an irresponsible assessment i do and i think it's really um you know something to be said
when you actually have the means to uh not only support your children but to support the village
right um the village i am not sure someone just asked what is about joe budden i have no idea what
joe budden's problem is with me i have no clue i think joe budden turned out to be a real funny style
nigga i've known joe budden since i was 19 i've never had a problem with joe budden until joe budden
started putting my name started putting my name in his mouth to use me as content i have absolutely
no idea why he thinks that is acceptable i have never had an issue with joe budden i have never
talked sideways about joe budden until joe budden started talking sideways about me so no clue
i genuinely have no clue the last time i saw joe budden he was doing smart funny and black in brooklyn
in 2018 uh and we had a great time you know so i have no idea he's making millions of dollars so i have
no idea why uh he would be distracted by me none so joe budden if you're listening if you're
watching um you have my phone number so i'm not sure what it is and i'm not sure why you think it's
acceptable to to yuck it up with your co-hosts um about me when they've actually never met me but you
have i know no idea but you know people don't have character so that's why that's why um you know
but i again i don't feel calling women out of their name i don't feel calling i don't feel like i don't
like for instance so to be honest like when people know me and they use me as content i have a real issue
with that right i have a real issue with people using me as content who know me right like if
you're interviewing somebody don't bring me up don't use me as content if you are making your videos
you know like when i was on uh club shay shay and then i see people who know me people who have
opened for me on tour etc and then they are making videos about me no absolutely not correct hemma they
are capitalizing off of me and i absolutely find issue with that so uh and for what it's worth i've
moved beyond that you know we're we're talking about real upper level high vibrational conversations
on a regular basis in my spaces i want to shout out everybody who attended the amandaland summit this
weekend it was an incredible experience to host so many dope individuals who are mindfully moving into
how to apply humanism um who are mindfully moving into uh political education and organizing as a source
of empowerment and a source of um elevation and to to be able to facilitate a space like that
was really incredible like if anything this is what i made money in that shitty place of hollywood to do
is to be able to create spaces like this and not have to ask or wait for like sums of money to arrive
um you know thankfully i did have friends of mine who uh were willing to donate scholarships to
individuals who were trying to come to the event but didn't have enough bread to pay for the the airfare
and hotel but they could but they were able to get their registration covered the registration fee was
two hundred dollars they got all their meals paid they got access to all the events um and they got
community and i really feel like i stepped into purpose in a whole other way in being able to facilitate
this because it happened with such ease right it happened with with such um gracefulness and it felt like
flow right and that's ideally what we want we want flow so you know when i hear these conversations
that are being had around things that are simply just distractions they're not really um things that are
helpful to what is coming at us i consider it to be um telling you know i consider it to be telling
that this is not where the masses should be listening i think that there is something very valuable
to distraction that um revitalizes that replenishes that reinvigorates right i think that's absolutely
very necessary and i think that's something different than what a lot of these podcasts are doing
um so you know um the work that i try to do when it comes to quote-unquote distraction
is more is about actually creating spaces for
interaction right like that's the goal creating spaces for interaction so that you can be taken
out of your mind which might be um you know really just overwhelmed
and able and allowing you to come into uh to come to bring your to get out of your thoughts
stop asking me about trey reed i have spoken about trey reed over and over and over again and i hate when
you all come in my chat and make demands of what i need to be speaking about based on what you want me
to speak about i'm clearly in flow i'm talking right now cut it out
if you want to see my thoughts on trey reed go look at all the content that i've done on trey reed
it is a demand when you post it several times you igbonayo
do y'all repeat yourselves to folks in real time like 10 times until they respond
no as for speaking i have a booking form on my website amandaseals.com also on my instagram bio
it says for booking uh there's a link there you don't need people in the comments to explain rosh
hashanah to you why why do you need people to explain that to you you can go find that out
yourself we have to be far more self-sufficient you don't need someone in here to tell you that
yep none of us made it to the rapture y'all sure they make you chuckle because i'll be like what is
going on you got one more time to ask me a question about uppercase him you got one more time i was on
rerun a hollywood game night i did not enjoy that that was the longest taping that taping was super
long and i don't like games that that don't challenge my brain and it's really games kind of
like um like parlor games good evening ahmed and then when we finally did get to play a game
that uses our brain my buzzer wouldn't work i was hot i was hot sending love your way as well
i made it look fun okay because i was like get me out of here and it was freezing you know how cold
it got to be for me to remember how cold it was it was so cold in that studio lord i remember
that was a cold like how i remember the cold on the uh obama's inauguration on obama's inauguration
day child the cold on obama's inauguration day my toes will never forget my toes will never forget
because i really was like oh i'm gonna like i'm gonna die of hypothermia i'm about to die right here
they had to open the smithsonian because it was so cold i saw you let people in the smithsonian
and now when i think back like you really was out there in the cold for an inauguration
that's some bullshit that's some bullshit
so anywho i'm not sure why this thing ain't letting me log in to ship
station but i need to ship some shit out so we need to get this figured out um so i'm gonna go
so i can troubleshoot but everybody have a great rest of your day and um careful um careful the
rapture don't get you careful the rapture don't get you all right now all right cats